http://www.towshop.com/privacy_security.htm

Privacy and Security Policy
Shop online at Towshop 24 hours a day 7 days a week. It's easy, safe and secure.
Ordering
Credit Card security is #1 with us. We use
SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology for ordering online.
We encrypt all personal information you give us when you order from us. Providing encrypted information online is as safe as providing it over the phone.
Just look for the https: in the address bar of the shopping cart checkout pages. That will tell you that you are on a secure page.
Most of the reported credit card fraud over the Internet has involved people emailing their credit card account numbers to merchants, or web sites accepting credit cards without using any security protocols.By clicking
the "GeoTrust" secure site seal on our "Online Shopping Catalog" page you can verify our authenticity and the security of our ordering process.
Personal Information
We do not sell, trade, loan or in any other way give your personal information to anyone. All personal information you give us stays with us.
We do from time to time run specials on our site and may notify you by email with your permission.
Cookies
Cookies are used to keep track of items you put in your shopping cart. We do not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer.
Cookies do not provide us with access to any credit card information. Again, the only personal information we have will be supplied by you.
Home Page
Copyright © 2000-2020 TowShop LLC All rights
reserved.
NEWSLETTER
Join our mailing list to receive updates on new arrivals and special offers.
Subscribe
